import { quizQuestions } from '../types/quiz'
export const reactquestionlist: quizQuestions[] = [
    {
        question: 'What is the name of React.js Developer ?',
        options: ['Jordan mike', 'Jordan Lee','Jordan Walke', 'Tim Lee'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Everything in React is a _____________ ',
        options: ['Module', 'Component', 'Package',' Class'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'What is Babel?',
        options: ['A transpiler', 'An interpreter', 'A Compiler','Both Compiler and Transpilar'],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'In React what is used to pass data to a component from outside?',
        options: ['setState', 'render with arguments', 'props','PropTypes'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What is a react.js in MVC?',
        options: ['Middleware','Controller', 'Model','Router'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'In React, component properties should be kept in an object called?',
        options: ['Component', 'Super', 'State','Props'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What function allows you to render React content in an HTML page?',
        options: ['React.mount()', 'ReactDOM.render()','ReactDOM.start()','React.render()'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'At the highest level, React components have lifecycle events that fall into',
        options: ['Destruction', 'Initialization', 'State/Property Updates','All of these'],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'React supports all the syntax of ........',
        options: ['ES6', 'Redux', 'Native Java','None of the above'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following is the correct data flow sequence of flux concept?',
        options: ['Action->Dispatcher->View->Store', 'Action->Dispatcher->Store->View', 'Action->Store->Dispatcher->View','None of the above'],
        answer: 2
    }
];